

Agung Tri Prasetyo

I am ussually called as auf. I am last semester student of Computer Engineering of Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya. I ever learned about AI when I was still joined in Robotics Laboratoirum Campus (1 Year). Lately, I am learning about Front End Web Development and Human Computer Interaction (UI/UX) since I got it in the 8th semester. For now, I'm still learning about React Js Framework.

Personal Details

D.O.B : Kediri, 13th February 1997

Domicile : Plemahan, Kediri, East Java, 64155

Linkedin : linkedin.com/in/agungtpras

Portfolio : auf.my.id

Phone Number & WA : +62888-0514-4004

: auf@tuta.io Email

Skills

 Typography = able Javascript = a little = able • C = able Prototyping • C++ HTML = able = a little CSS = able Python = a little

Experience

Yolla Wedding Planner (Jombang, Indonesia)

Freelancer (April 2020 - now)

I help make the ongoing wedding event get a success

Trainsys Robot Education, MIN Kauman (Surabaya, Indonesia)

Extracurricular Mentor (September 2019 - now)

Teach basic electronics for robot to student. (closed during the pandemic)

PT. Pembangunan Perumahan (Surabaya, Indonesia)

Internship, Site Engineer (January 2019 - April 2019)

- I implemented Internet of Construction. My mentor asked me to make Fire Warning System in construction. I used nodeMcu as microcontroller and c language as programming language, Infrared sensor as fire sensor, MQ-2 as gas sensor and Blynk IoT Platform as software side.
- Sometimes I help the HSE/K3 division to do inspections on apartment building.

Robotics Laboratory, Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya(Surabaya, Indonesia)

Volunteer, Al Programmer Assistant of Eepis Robot Soccer on Wheel (October 2017 -August 2018)

- I help the AI Programmer as assistant to program the robot. I program the robot strategy based on the rule of Kontes Robot Indonesia.
- Sometimes I help in hardware division.

Trainsys Robot Education, MTSN 3 (Surabaya, Indonesia)

Extracurricular Mentor (March 2017 - June 2017)

Teach basic electronics for robot to student

AHASS Perak Jombang (Jombang, Indonesia) Administration Staff (February 2016 - July 2016)

• I made daily report to be sent in MPM Center.

- Do some transactions with customer.
- Following up the customer, I reminded the customer to service their motor. • Sometimes I help the technician to fixing/serviced the customer's motor

Computer Center, Universitas Negeri Surabaya(Surabaya, Indonesia) Internship, Network Technician(January 2014 - May 2014)

I help the technician to do network installation and repairation.

Educational Background

Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya (2016-now)

D4 Computer Engineering

- Participated in LKMM Pra-TD 2016
- Participated in LKMM TD 2016
- Participated in E-Bio Management Training 2016
- Become Young Enterpreneur Staff in UKKI PENS 2016
- Become Young Enterpreneur Staff in Ukm Seni Islami PENS 2017 Particiated in Jember Line Tracer Competition 2017
- Participated in Kontes Robot Indonesia Regional IV 2018 Participated in Kotes Robot Indonesia Nasional 2018
- Become Volunteer as Liaison Officier in Pediatric cancer foundation 2019

3rd Vocational High School Jombang (2012-2015)

• Become Volunteer as Liaison Officier in Yatim Mandiri 2019

- Computer and Network Engineering • Become Remaja Masjid staff, we held Independency Competition between all classes
- with OSIS 2014 • Be a graduate with the second best NEM (3.6)